function QuestionGenerator(count = 5) {
  const questions = [
    {
      question: "What is the capital city?",
      options: ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Ibadan", "Jos"],
      answer: "Abuja"
    },
    {
      question: "Which was the first mobile telecom network?",
      options: ["GLO", "MTN", "ECONET", "CELTEL"],
      answer: "ECONET"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the population in millions?",
      options: ["186", "100", "40", "86"],
      answer: "186"
    },
    {
      question: "One is not a major language?",
      options: ["Yoruba", "Swahili", "Hausa", "Ibo"],
      answer: "Swahili"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the national currency?",
      options: ["Dollars", "Euro", "Yen", "Naira"],
      answer: "Naira"
    },
    {
      question: "Which colonised Nigeria?",
      options: ["Britian", "USA", "Portugal", "Russia"],
      answer: "Britian"
    },
    {
      question: "What year was independence?",
      options: ["1970", "1960", "1950", "1980"],
      answer: "1960"
    },
    {
      question: "Which is not a state in Nigeria?",
      options: ["Delta", "Rivers", "Kano", "Accra"],
      answer: "Accra"
    },
    {
      question: "Which was the first ever capital city?",
      options: ["Lagos", "Abuja", "Ibadan", "Jos"],
      answer: "Lagos"
    },
    {
      question: "Which was the first church in Nigeria?",
      options: ["St. Peters", "St. Luke", "St. John", "St Micheal"],
      answer: "St. Peters"
    }
  ];

  return(
    questions.sort(function(){return (Math.random() - Math.random())}).slice(0, count)
  )
}

export default QuestionGenerator;